http://www.nowsmart.com/privacy-policy.html

NowSmartProductsAudio Record WizardNowSmart CutDownloadBuySupportNowSmart Customer Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting www.nowsmart.com. NowSmart highly respects the privacy of our customers, and we take the issue of your privacy very seriously. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, other than for the purpose of fulfilling orders.
What we collect and how we use it
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, physical address, email address, and credit card information. This data is only used for the purpose of fulfilling orders or communicating with customers.
NowSmart uses secure server hosted by Paypal, FastSpring, Regnow or other third party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer's personal information before it is sent to us, including name, physical address, email address, and credit card information. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information.
Links to Other Web Sites
This site may be linked to other web sites on the Internet. NowSmart is not responsible for the content of such sites. Your use of these other linked web sites is subject to the respective terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked sites.
What about cookies
"Cookies" are small pieces of information saved as small text files. Like many other companies, NowSmart uses "cookies" in order to improve the overall site experience. These cookies do not store sensitive data.
Policy Changes
We reserves the right to change this privacy policy, and may update this policy at any time by posting additions or modifications on this web page. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this web site will be subject to the then-current privacy policy.
Approved by Norton Safe Web
HomeContact usPrivacy PolicySitemap
Copyright © 2018 NowSmart. All rights reserved.
